<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>

<title>nosebleeds</title>
<link></link>
<description>A minimal blog template for tinyjam.</description>
<atom:link href="/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

   <item>
     <title>New Pizza</title>
     <link>/posts/new-pizza.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/new-pizza.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<p>I call it new pizza because it has a different process than you are probably used to. You cook the the dough first on the stove top, then you cook the cheese and toppings under the broiler. So before you start this recipe make sure your oven has a broiler setting (maybe all do? I have no idea, i only started using it like this year and it rules for melting cheese). Anyways ahere we gooo</p>
<p>* recipe requires at least one frying pan you can put in the oven (cast iron is best)</p>
<p><strong>Dough recipe (makes 2 dough balls/pizzas)</strong></p>
<p>In a big bowl (we&#39;ll call it our <em>wet bowl)</em> mix:<br>1.5 cups of warm water<br>2 tablespoons sugar<br>1.5 teaspoons active dry yeast (sure other yeasts work, this is just the one I have used)<br>2 tablespoons olive oil</p>
<p>In another bowl (the <em>dry bowl</em>) mix:<br>3 cups AP flour<br>1 teaspoon salt<br><br>Now combine the stuff, I like to use a wooden spoon first, add the dry mix to the wet mix about a cup at a time and stir with the wooden spoon until its too hard cause youre a little wimpy loser. Once your forearms wuss out you can drop the spoon and then use your dirty hands and work it until its all mixed together in a sticky dough ball. Seriously the more you work it the better so fud with it for like 5 minutes. OR if you have a stand mixer you can just pour all this shit in there and whip it in there for 5 minutes. Anyways its dough, jus tdo it</p>
<p>so doughs mixed now. now grease a big bowl with some butter or non-stick, and throw the ball in there and cover with a damp towel and leave it in a warm area for an hour</p>
<p>It has risen like christ on either Easter or Christmas I don&#39;t know who cares, take it out of the greasy bowl and roll it around in a little flour. Once you have a nice little cooperative dough ball, cut it in half so you have 2 little cute little baby dough balls hehe.</p>
<p><strong>Cooking Time</strong></p>
<p>In your oven safe frying pan drop in like a tablespoon ish of olive oil, pinch of each kosher salt, garlic salt, oregano, italian seasoning, and parsley. Rub it all around with your fingies or a brush, make sure you get the whole pan. </p>
<p>Now to stretch the dough ball into a circle to fit in the pan. I don&#39;t know how to do this very well, it sucks, you can try to do it in the air like you know what youre doing or you can just push it down and out for a while trying not to rip it, anyways you gotta get the dough ball into the pan to look like a real pizza, so battle with that until it&#39;s satisfactory. Here&#39;s what mine looked like.</p>
<p><img src="/images/pizza1.png" alt="Pizza dough"></p>
<p>Now here comes the &quot;new pizza&quot; part -- turn on one of your stove top elements on high, and put the frying pan on it. Now you gotta babysit it, grab a flipper and just keep checking the bottom, you want it to be crispy, partially burnt even in places, like you just keep checking it until the bottom looks like a proper ass pizza bottom. Once you think the bottom looks superb you turn OFF the burner. This should take like max 5 minutes.</p>
<p>So now you&#39;ve got the bottom of the crust perfect. So now you just dress your pizza like you normally would. put some sauce on it (I recommend PC tomato &amp; basil pasta sauce if you&#39;re lazy like me), then put your toppings on, then your cheese, then whatever, I like to dice up garlic and sprinkle that around. I also like some shredded parmasean or pecorino romano whatever that is. Also HIGHLY RECOMMEND some provolone cheese chunks (it makes the cheese thicker and better I think), ALSO HIGHLY RECOMMENDED if you got perpperoni on there, you sprinly some fennel seeds on there, ye!!! Anyways top&#39;em up like you like.</p>
<p><img src="/images/pizza3.png" alt="Pizza ready to go"></p>
<p>Now make sure you have a rack on the top slot of your oven, and then crank on the BROIL, and put the pizza right under it. Now keep your EYE ON IT, it&#39;s quick. It will be like 3 minutes. Just keep opening the stove and pulling it out and checking. Eventually it will look like the best pizza you&#39;ve ever seen. When it looks like that then you are done. </p>
<p><img src="/images/pizza4.png" alt="broiler"></p>
<p>Take it out and give it a few minutes to chill out, then chop it up and dig in bruh</p>
<p><img src="/images/pizza5.png" alt="done pizza"></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Friday Feels - FS Green | Appelsap Festival x Boiler Room DJ set</title>
     <link>/posts/friday-feels-fs-green-appelsap-festival-x-boiler-room-dj-set.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/friday-feels-fs-green-appelsap-festival-x-boiler-room-dj-set.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<p>FS Green is always good, but on Fridays especially - LFGGGGGGG</p>
<iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" allow="autoplay" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/278637837&color=%23ff5500&auto_play=false&hide_related=false&show_comments=true&show_user=true&show_reposts=false&show_teaser=true"></iframe>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Today I&apos;m listening to: Smirk - LP</title>
     <link>/posts/today-im-listening-to-smirk-lp.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/today-im-listening-to-smirk-lp.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<iframe style="border: 0; width: 350px; height: 470px;" src="https://bandcamp.com/EmbeddedPlayer/album=324038407/size=large/bgcol=ffffff/linkcol=0687f5/tracklist=false/transparent=true/" seamless><a href="https://smirk1.bandcamp.com/album/lp">LP by Smirk</a></iframe>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Today I&apos;m listening to: The Natural M*n Band - LIVING IN A CHEMICAL WORLD WITH THE NATURAL MAN BAND</title>
     <link>/posts/today-im-listening-to-living-in-a-chemical-world-with-the-natural-man-band-the-natural-m-n-band.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/today-im-listening-to-living-in-a-chemical-world-with-the-natural-man-band-the-natural-m-n-band.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<iframe style="border: 0; width: 350px; height: 720px;" src="https://bandcamp.com/EmbeddedPlayer/album=360810927/size=large/bgcol=ffffff/linkcol=0687f5/transparent=true/" seamless><a href="https://siliconeprairie.bandcamp.com/album/living-in-a-chemical-world-with-the-natural-man-band">LIVING IN A CHEMICAL WORLD WITH THE NATURAL MAN BAND by The Natural M*n Band</a></iframe>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Today I&apos;m listening to: GEE TEE - FAST Demo</title>
     <link>/posts/today-im-listening-to-gee-too-fast-demo.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/today-im-listening-to-gee-too-fast-demo.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<iframe style="border: 0; width: 350px; height: 621px;" src="https://bandcamp.com/EmbeddedPlayer/album=802494099/size=large/bgcol=ffffff/linkcol=0687f5/transparent=true/" seamless><a href="https://geeteeband.bandcamp.com/album/fast-demo">FAST Demo by GEE TEE</a></iframe>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Cheesy Dawg Bread</title>
     <link>/posts/cheesy-dawg-bread.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/cheesy-dawg-bread.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<p>There&#39;s a place in London called the Dawghouse, their garlic bread rules and this recipe reminds me of theirs.</p>
<ul>
<li>preheat oven to 425</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>In a mixing bowl mix this stuff together</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>1 cup of shredded cheese (cheddar, mozza, marble, or a combo of cheeses whatever you want)</li>
<li>1/4 cup mayo</li>
<li>3 garlic gloves, minced</li>
<li>2 tablespoons grated parm (or pecorino romano)</li>
<li>2 teaspoons Italian seasoning</li>
<li>pinch of kosher salt</li>
<li>pinch of ground black pepper</li>
<li>2 tablespoons of parsley (I just use dried parsley flakes, so I do slightly less than 2 full tablespoons)</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="/images/garlic_bread.png" alt="garlic bread spread"></p>
<p><strong>Bread</strong></p>
<p>You can use whatever you want, a baguette, a couple sub buns, hot dog/hamburg buns. I prefer taking 2 sub buns, cutting them in half lengthwise. I feel thats the traditional pub style.</p>
<p>Whatever bread you go with, spread some margarine on there, or don&#39;t, I don&#39;t care. Im a pig, so I do this.</p>
<p><strong>SO now you just spread your mixture out on your bread vessel.</strong> </p>
<p><img src="/images/garlic_bread2.png" alt="sporeaded on breaded"></p>
<p><strong>sporeaded on breaded!</strong></p>
<p>chrow it in the oven in the mid rack for 11 minutes. Done</p>
<p>I forgot to take picture when I took it out, but it&#39;s gonna look like garlic bread. trust me!</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>My snake died</title>
     <link>/posts/my-snake-died.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/my-snake-died.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="und" dir="ltr">😭😭😭😭 <a href="https://t.co/NBtTYQUm2b">pic.twitter.com/NBtTYQUm2b</a></p>&mdash; Tristan (@TristanGHill) <a href="https://twitter.com/TristanGHill/status/1505271932861751308?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 19, 2022</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Gary Borthwick Says</title>
     <link>/posts/gary-borthwick-says.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/gary-borthwick-says.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EcfX6bJhO48" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Asian stir fry thing</title>
     <link>/posts/asian-stir-fry-thing.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/asian-stir-fry-thing.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<p>I don&#39;t know if it&#39;s Asian really, but it has soy sauce in it. I like to prep this one at lunch and let it marinate until I&#39;m ready to cook for dinner.</p>
<p><strong>Serves 2 people.</strong></p>
<p>Put all this stuff into a medium size bowl, something you can seal shut, or just put glad wrap on to keep air tight if possible:</p>
<ul>
<li>2 skinless, boneless chicken breasts chopped into cubes</li>
<li>2 cloves of minced garlic</li>
<li>shred a chunk of ginger in there the size of your thumb</li>
<li>1/2 tablespoon of olive oil</li>
<li>1/2 teaspoon kosher salt (or any salt)</li>
<li>1/2 teaspoon pepper</li>
</ul>
<p>So yeah, mix that stuff all together and throw it covered into the fridge for a couple hours if possible. If you don&#39;t have time to marinate it probably doesn&#39;t even matter (maybe it does, I have no idea I&#39;m not a food doctor), I just like getting this step out of the way so it&#39;s less to do later.</p>
<p><strong>Prep to cook:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>the meal takes about 10 minutes to cook once you start the burner, so you should start your rice to accommodate for that (I buy big boxes of Minute Rice brown rice (pic below) and just microwave a cup of rice, and a cup of water for 10 minutes, so easy)</li>
<li>chunk up at least half a head of broccoli</li>
<li>at least 1 pepper (red, yellow, or orange) sliced, not diced</li>
<li>maybe 2-3 &quot;discs&quot; of red onion, sliced not diced (you know what a disc is, don&#39;t give me that)</li>
<li>crush 15 almonds or peanuts or cashews (I usually put them in a ziplock and beat it up)</li>
<li>have ready to add: soy sauce, red pepper flakes, peanut butter, sriracha </li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Time to cook:</strong></p>
<p>In a large pan (I like a wok for this, or something cast iron), heat up a 1/2 tablespoon of sesame oil (canola oil if you don&#39;t have sesame, or any oil I have no idea what I&#39;m talking about Im not a food scientist). Heat it on high, like 8.5/10. Once that&#39;s heated up (you can flick water at it and it sizzles) chuck your whole marinated mixture of crap in there and stir it around for a minute or two, until the chicken is starting to brown.</p>
<p>Next you want to throw in the broccoli, peppers, onions, stir that around for a minute or two.</p>
<p>Once you think everything is more or less cooked you can add the rest of the ingredients and stir around. I will typically add I don&#39;t know a tablespoon of soy sauce, a tablespoon of peanut butter, maybe a teaspoon of red pepper flakes, and a teaspoon of sriracha but really the amount of those ingredients depends on what you want. Add more soy sauce for a saltier flavour, peanut butter for more sweetness, red pepper flakes and sriracha for more heat. I&#39;ve never actually measured these ingredients, I just throw them in an taste as I go. Anyways mix all that up, stir around for another minute or two until it&#39;s all cooked and mixed through. It should be sort of sticky/chunky at this point. Serve it on top of the rice, <strong>done!</strong></p>
<p>Should end up looking kinda like this</p>
<p><img src="/images/stir-fry.png" alt=""></p>
<p>Rice I buy</p>
<p><img src="/images/minute-rice.png" alt=""></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Ranchero Wrap</title>
     <link>/posts/ranchero-wrap.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/ranchero-wrap.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<p>So this is my take on an overpriced wrap I used to pay for almost weekly when working in office downtown. Place was called &quot;Salad Bowl&quot;, the wrap is called the &quot;Ranchero Wrap&quot;. This is my copycat recipe, feeds 2:</p>
<p><strong>Ingredients:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>2 large tortilla wraps</li>
<li>1 big or 2 small chicken breast</li>
<li>2 discs of red onion (more or less) diced</li>
<li>half a tomato diced</li>
<li>1 avocado</li>
<li>1/2 cup of cheddar cheese</li>
<li>iceberg lettuce (enough for 2 big macs) I measure iceberg lettuce in big macs</li>
<li>tsp chilli powder</li>
<li>ranch dressing or creaming dressing (pictured)</li>
<li>optional - bacon crumble</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="/images/creamy.png" alt=""></p>
<p><strong>Pre-prep:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>cube 1 big or 2 small chicken breast</li>
<li>brown that in a non-stick in olive oil, salt, and pepper a couple hours before dinner, I usually do this at lunch.</li>
<li>put it in a bowl or something covered with saran wrap, and put in the fridge to cool.</li>
</ul>
<p>Whatever you do, just make sure the chicken is cold. This is a cold wrappopp buddy. You don&#39;t want no moist chicken chunks, it tastes like eating a petri dish.</p>
<p>So you and your chicken (c)hunks, you&#39;re almost done. </p>
<p><strong>The prep:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>throw down your tortilla wrap on some tinfoil if you fancy</li>
<li>put half the chicken clumps down on each</li>
<li>line with ranch dressing, or garlic parm dressing</li>
<li>sprinkle a 1/2 tsp or so of chilli powder on each</li>
<li>sprinkle half the cheese, half the tomato, the onion, lettuce, and avocado on each</li>
<li>wrap&#39;em up bro! <strong>DONE</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>If you&#39;re lucky it&#39;ll look something like this image I stole from google images:</p>
<p><img src="/images/ranchero.png" alt=""></p>]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
