<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>

<title>nosebleeds</title>
<link></link>
<description>A minimal blog template for tinyjam.</description>
<atom:link href="/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

   <item>
     <title>Ranchero Wrap</title>
     <link>/posts/ranchero-wrap.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/ranchero-wrap.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<p>So this is my take on an overpriced wrap I used to pay for almost weekly when working in office downtown. Place was called &quot;Salad Bowl&quot;, the wrap is called the &quot;Ranchero Wrap&quot;. This is my copycat recipe, feeds 2:</p>
<p><strong>Ingredients:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>2 large tortilla wraps</li>
<li>1 big or 2 small chicken breast</li>
<li>2 discs of red onion (more or less) diced</li>
<li>half a tomato diced</li>
<li>1 avocado</li>
<li>1/2 cup of cheddar cheese</li>
<li>iceberg lettuce (enough for 2 big macs) I measure iceberg lettuce in big macs</li>
<li>tsp chilli powder</li>
<li>ranch dressing or creaming dressing (pictured)</li>
<li>optional - bacon crumble</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="/images/creamy.png" alt=""></p>
<p><strong>Pre-prep:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>cube 1 big or 2 small chicken breast</li>
<li>brown that in a non-stick in olive oil, salt, and pepper a couple hours before dinner, I usually do this at lunch.</li>
<li>put it in a bowl or something covered with saran wrap, and put in the fridge to cool.</li>
</ul>
<p>Whatever you do, just make sure the chicken is cold. This is a cold wrappopp buddy. You don&#39;t want no moist chicken chunks, it tastes like eating a petri dish.</p>
<p>So you and your chicken (c)hunks, you&#39;re almost done. </p>
<p><strong>The prep:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>throw down your tortilla wrap on some tinfoil if you fancy</li>
<li>put half the chicken clumps down on each</li>
<li>line with ranch dressing, or garlic parm dressing</li>
<li>sprinkle a 1/2 tsp or so of chilli powder on each</li>
<li>sprinkle half the cheese, half the tomato, the onion, lettuce, and avocado on each</li>
<li>wrap&#39;em up bro! <strong>DONE</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>If you&#39;re lucky it&#39;ll look something like this image I stole from google images:</p>
<p><img src="/images/ranchero.png" alt=""></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Heavy Discipline - Heavy Discipline</title>
     <link>/posts/heavy-discipline-heavy-discipline.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/heavy-discipline-heavy-discipline.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<p>fogettaboutit hardcore... good stuff! Dope artwork too</p>
<iframe style="border: 0; width: 350px; height: 470px;" src="https://bandcamp.com/EmbeddedPlayer/album=1529818092/size=large/bgcol=ffffff/linkcol=0687f5/tracklist=false/transparent=true/" seamless><a href="https://painkillerrecords.bandcamp.com/album/pkr-082-heavy-discipline">PKR-082: Heavy Discipline by Heavy Discipline</a></iframe>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>ANIMA - Wheat</title>
     <link>/posts/02.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/02.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<p>Anything this ANIMA person does rules. I find it so calming, but at the same time so anxious and energizing. A lot of it has recognizable riddims, or lyrics but always altered to the point where it&#39;s not always obvious upon first listen. This would be like my favourite genre if it were one, but it&#39;s literally just this person as far as I know. And suprising I like it eventhough there are barely any drums. Hook me up in the comments if you know something else close to this! </p>
<iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" allow="autoplay" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/1140236119&color=%23ff5500&auto_play=false&hide_related=false&show_comments=true&show_user=true&show_reposts=false&show_teaser=true"></iframe>

<p>Here are some more of my favs:</p>
<iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" allow="autoplay" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/719843425&color=%23ff5500&auto_play=false&hide_related=false&show_comments=true&show_user=true&show_reposts=false&show_teaser=true"></iframe>

<iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" allow="autoplay" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/924476995&color=%23ff5500&auto_play=false&hide_related=false&show_comments=true&show_user=true&show_reposts=false&show_teaser=true"></iframe>

<iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" allow="autoplay" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/840519439&color=%23ff5500&auto_play=false&hide_related=false&show_comments=true&show_user=true&show_reposts=false&show_teaser=true"></iframe>

<iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" allow="autoplay" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/529221045&color=%23ff5500&auto_play=false&hide_related=false&show_comments=true&show_user=true&show_reposts=false&show_teaser=true"></iframe>

<iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" allow="autoplay" src="https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/570971970&color=%23ff5500&auto_play=false&hide_related=false&show_comments=true&show_user=true&show_reposts=false&show_teaser=true"></iframe>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
     <title>Grandma&apos;s buns</title>
     <link>/posts/01.html</link>
     <guid>/posts/01.html</guid>
     <description><![CDATA[<p>Not actually my grandma&#39;s recipe, but they encompass the best part about them, <strong>YOU CANN RIP THEM APART WITHOUT A KNIFE YOU WEAK LOSER.</strong> </p>
<p><img src="/images/tore.gif" alt=""></p>
<p>yeah man, thats why I like them. I&#39;ve seen them called pull-apart buns, or cloverleaf buns. anyways here&#39;s my recipe:</p>
<p>Get 2 big bowls</p>
<p><strong>In one bowl:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>3.5 cups + 2 tablespoons all purpose flour</li>
<li>1.5 teaspons salt</li>
<li>mix that together</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>In other bowl:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>2 tablespoons of sugar</li>
<li>2 teaspons of instant yeast - you can use active yeast or whatever too, this is just easier and what i have used</li>
<li>4 tablespoons of softened butter</li>
<li>1 cup + 2.5 tablespoons of Warm milk</li>
</ul>
<p>Once you have the 2 bowls ready to go, start pouring the flour/salt bowl into the other bowl about a cup at a time and mixing with a wooden spoon or something. </p>
<p>Once you have all the shit combined, just keep mixing with the wooden spoon until it&#39;s really sticky. </p>
<p>Then wash your hands, roll up your sleeves, and put your hands in there and just keep rolling it around and folding it in on itself for like 5 minutes or until it looks and acts like dough. </p>
<p>Wash the now empty bowl and dry it off, then grease it up with some butter or pam or something. </p>
<p>Take your doughball and throw it in the greased bowl and put a damp dish drying towel over the bowl and put it somewhere warmish in your house. </p>
<p>Let it sit for 60-90 minutes.</p>
<p>Grab a muffin tray (12 spots), grease up the holes by rubbing some margerine or butter around in them with parchment paper.</p>
<p>Take out your dough bowl and throw it down on a surface witha bit of flour, roll it around. </p>
<p>Then you need to chop this focker up into 12 equally sized balls. I usually chop it into 3 equal pieces, then from each of those I chop them into 4. SO I have 12 ballssssss. Then I cut each in half, then each of those pieces i fold a bit into a ball. Then place 2 balss in each place in the muffin tray! </p>
<p>Should look like this kinda but only 2 balls</p>
<p><img src="/images/buns.png" alt=""></p>
<p>Lay your dish towel on top of the rack and let it chill for another hour.</p>
<p>Preheat your oven to 350. Take off the towel and put the buns in the oven for 22 minutes.</p>
<p>Melt some butter, take the buns out and then brush some butter on top of them. <strong>DONE</strong></p>
<p>Should look like this kinda but only 2 balls</p>
<p><img src="/images/buns_done.png" alt=""></p>]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
